我们回顾第二节当凯瑟琳调用一个
Remember back in lesson two when Katherine used a
异步任务连接刷新键来更新
AsyncTask hooked up to a refresh button to update
数据吗？Rato就谈到这是怎样的一个
our data? Rato talked about how that was a
不好的方法，因为异步任务没有和
bad idea, because the AsyncTask is not tied to
activity的生命周期捆绑在一起。虚拟机会一直保持
the activity life cycle. The virtual machine will hold
activity对象，只要异步任务处在运行状态
on to the activity object as long as the
即使在安卓已经通知onDestroy后
AsyncTask is running, even after Android has called onDestroy
希望他被丢弃。
for the activity and expect it to be discarded.
如果你旋转你的手机，这个行为将
If you rotate your phone, the behavior is to
破坏你的activity然后实例化一个新的。
destroy your activity and instantiate a new one. The
现在单纯的异步任务实施有俩条线路来尝试
naive AsyncTask implementation now has two threads trying to
实现相同的更新，等等。关键是，
perform the same update, and so forth. The point is,
它对于冗长的后台操作的情况并不是最好的解决方法
it's not the best pattern for a potentially very
比如获取网络服务
long background operation, such as fetching from web services. If
如果你将app转到了后台，异步任务将会继续
you leave the app, the asynctask will continue to
运行只要你的活动进程一直处于活跃状态，
run for as long as your process is kept alive,
只不过运行在一个较低的优先权下，然后你的进程
but will run at a low priority, and your process
会被优先释放掉，当系统服务
will be the first thing to be killed if the device
需要更多的资源。而且还会有一个更大的问题，你的app
needs more resources. And there's a bigger problem. Your app
必须在屏幕上处于可见状态且运行在前台并第一时间实例化
has to be visible and running in the foreground to instantiate
了异步任务。因为我们开始一个
the task in the first place. Because we started a
任务，当我们打开app去更新天气，
task, to update the weather when we started the app, this
如果天气总是快速变化严重影响用户体验。所以
can have undesirable behavior if the weather changes rapidly. So
我们现在要学习正确的方法来执行更新。
now we're going to learn the right way to perform updates.
我们需要当app在前台运行得时候，
We'll want to automate the process while the app is in
它会自动更新。但更重要的是，我们想要app能够
the foreground. But even more importantly, we want the app to get
在后台以最小的电量消耗来实现有规律的更新。那将
regular updates in the background with minimal battery drain. That will
是我们后续在介绍天气信息通知时候，在这门课程
be especially important later in this
里面最重要的部分。
lesson when we introduce weather notifications.